Okay.
So let's summarize what we've learned regarding
Global Applications in AWS.
First, we've seen the global DNS Route 53,
and this is a great way for you to route users,
to the closer to deployment with the least latency
and is going to be very helpful as well
when we define disaster recovery strategies.
So we showed how to create records
and how to have them point from
host name to IP for example.
We've seen a global content delivery network,
CDN CloudFront,
and we've actually hooked it up to Amazon S3.
So the idea is that we were able to replicate
part of our application data into some AWS Edge Locations
and this allowed us to decrease latency.
And on top of it,
we were able to cache the common request in CloudFront,
which gives us improve user experience
and decreased latency.
Next, we have the S3 transfer acceleration
that actually is going to allow us to accelerate
global uploads and downloads into Amazon S3
and also leverages the Edge Locations of AWS.
Google Accelerator, yet again,
leverages these Edge Locations, the global network,
and this gives us an improved global application
availability and performance.
Next we've seen Outposts.
So this is more of how to extend our whole infrastructure.
So Outposts allow us to deploy these Outposts Racks
into our own data center to extend some AWS services.
So here we have the Cloud of AWS within our data center
on premises.
We have WaveLength and this is to bring in
services to the Edge thanks to the 5G networks
and give us ultra low latency application.
And finally, Local Zones.
Local Zones are allowing us to bring resources of AWS
to just compute database storage closer to your users,
for example, in Boston, Dallas, Miami, Chicago, and so on.
And this is going to be really, really good
when you have a latency sensitive application
that needs to have a very, very fast local access
in a specific region of the United States or the World.
But for now just the US.
Okay, so that's it for this lecture.
I hope you liked it.
And I will see you in the next lecture.